Pablo Kogan

Full-Stack Developer - Project Leader

CV in Inglish | CV en Español



About me

Full-Stack Developer with experience +20 years in developing innovative solutions, leading teams, and knowledge transfer. Additionally, I work as a teacher and manage extension, research, and innovation projects at the National University of Comahue. I am seeking new development challenges that provide tools to improve society and industry.

Personal

Pablo Kogan nationality: Argentina 1980

Areas of specialization

Full-Stack Developer • TDD
• CI/CD • DataData Analytics
and Modeling • PHP • JS
• Python • Docker • Linux

Other Skills

Team leadership. Very proactive with self learning and self managment skills. Ability to work on teams, learn and teach.

Interests

Free Software / AI / Electoral System / Learning Platform



WORK EXPERIENCE

2014-present | Full-Stack developer - Project Leader - IT Manager

Universidad Nacional del Comahue · Neuquén 9

Project Management, Project Architect, Software development in learning platform and electoral system. Manage extension, research, and innova-

tion projects.

2010-2014 Full-Stack developer

FREELANCE - CORTITOYALPIE · Neuquén 9

Software development of Oil&Gas | Games | Learning solutions.

2007-2010 Full-Stack developer - Project leader - IT Manager

ciar SA · Neuquén 💡

Software development of GIS to Oil&Gas solutions.

2005-present | Associate Professor

Universidad Nacional del Comahue · Neuguén ?

Teacher in Programming and Computer Theory Departments for Computer Science Bachelor Degree.



LANGUAGES

Spanish mother

Inglish • •

DEVELOPMENT AND PUBLICATIONS

hornero Competir+motivar+hornero= aprender

programación, in: TE&ET 2016.

gukena Gukena: escrutinio descentralizado para voto ponderado, in: JAIIO 2018.

wene Digital Certificate Management.

Programming

html, css

javascript

PHP

bash

sal

DEGREES

2020-present | Master in Computer Science | Universidad Nacional del Comahue · Neuquén ♥

2015-present | Master in Science, Technology and Innovation Universidad Nacional de Río Negro · Bariloche ♥

U•

1999–2006 | Bachelor in Computer Science

Universidad Nacional del Comahue · Neuquén 💡

